const sampleQuestions = [
  {
    question: '10 + 20',
    answer: 30,
  },
  {
    question: '11 + 22',
    answer: 33,
  },
  {
    question: '22 - 12',
    answer: 10,
  },
  {
    question: '111 x 20',
    answer: 2220,
  },
  {
    question: '112 + 20',
    answer: 132,
  },
  {
    question: '123 + 123',
    answer: 246,
  },
  {
    question: '4444 - 3333',
    answer: 1111,
  },
  {
    question: '2323 / 23',
    answer: 101,
  },
  {
    question: '2323 + 23',
    answer: 2346,
  },
  {
    question: '2323 - 23',
    answer: 2300,
  },
  {
    question: '33 / 11',
    answer: 3,
  },
  {
    question: '20 - 12',
    answer: 8,
  },
  {
    question: '144 - 44',
    answer: 100,
  },
]

export default sampleQuestions
